

Calum Website: cally.dev Mobile: 07951753329 Email: cal@cally.dev Github: callycodes.github.com

ABOUT ME

Passionate and explorative Software Developer with knowledge in many spectrums of coding. Experience in back-end logic, development of API interfaces, machine learning and scraping data. Understanding of automated services, fintech & trading applications, management and consumer systems. Strong curiosity in researching new technologies, frameworks and evolving intuitive projects collaboratively.

LANGUAGES, FRAMEWORKS & TOOLS

Proficiency in Python, Java, C#, Swift, PHP, HTML, JS, CSS and SQL. With application of Flask, Vue.js, Django, Node.js, Codeigniter and ability to store data securely using MySQL, PostgreSQL, Amazon Cognito and Firebase. Working knowledge with multiple IDEs such as VS Code, Eclipse, Google Colab, VS Studio and PyCharm to name a few. Daily usage of Github supported by my enjoyment for contribution and community.

EDUCATION

EXPECTED University of Westminster 2021/6

Software Engineering BEng on track for 1st class honours

2019/6 Samuel Whitbread Academy

3 A-Levels

Computer Science - C Mathematics - D Graphic Design - C

Samuel Whitbread Academy 2017/6

11 GCSEs

HOBBIES











PROJECTS

UniAccom Stack: Python, Vue.js Flask, JS, HTML, CSS, Google Maps API and PostgreSQL.

Student accomodation shortlisting tool, compare properties, travel distance & costs in a simple UI. View on my Github

WorkoutPal Stack: Vue.js, HTML, JS,

CSS, Firebase

Exercise planner and logger with advanced functionalities. Soon available on my Github

Email Fraud Al Stack: Python, Flask,

Google DialogueFlow

Detects unmatched company data, and uses AI to determine malicious intent. View on my Github

EXPERIENCE

CURRENT

Bedfordshire Bowls Website

Completely refresh and update the site and create a management system

2019-2020

Rozen Gallery

Worked with a student photographer to developer an interactive portfolio

2017-2018

Henlow Dog Racing Track

Waitered, coordinated seating of large groups and friendly front-of-house

2015-2017

Etonbury School Cleaner

Cleaned and organised floors, tables and learning spaces weekly.

2015

Westfest

Working with the military to develop a site for their final Westfest event.